Guide to the University of Pittsburgh Archives Audio Recordings Collection, 1950-2000 UA.Audio
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Research Findings, 1952-1993; VII.
  - International Monetary System - Conducted by Edward Berutsun, March 16, 1977; 1 reel-to-reel (Box 20, Reel 219)
  - US Foreign Aid - Conducted by Krause, March 30, 1977; 1 reel-to-reel (Box 21, Reel 221)
  - The United Nations: Today and Tomorrow? - Conducted by Richard N. Gardner, Philip Deane, William Moran, October 21, 1962; 1 reel-to-reel (Box 24, Reel 262)
  - Myths' of International Development - Conducted by F.M.C. Obi, Aldo Ferrer, Robert E. Asher, April 8, 1962; 1 reel-to-reel (Box 24, Reel 264)
  - Is A 'Grand Design' in Foreign Policy Possible? - Conducted by Thomas W. Wilson, Jr., William E. Moran, Rowland Ludden, January 28, 1962; 1 reel-to-reel (Box 24, Reel 265)
  - Women's Studies Colloquium, March 11, 1981; 1 reel-to-reel (Box 24, Reel 274)
  - Modern Techniques Linking Knowledge and Action, September 19, 1989; 1 cassette_tape (Box 28, Cassette 295)
  - American Society for Public Administration, October 24, 1969; 1 reel-to-reel (Box 7, Reel 59)
  - Faith and Today's World, 1970; 1 reel-to-reel (Box 7, Reel 56)
  - Study of Political Science Journals in Hillman Library - Conducted by Diane Luce, July 30, 1970; 1 reel-to-reel (Box 10, Reel 83)
  - Open University - Common Facilities Building, 1969; 1 reel-to-reel (Box 13, Reel 145)
  - "Henry Steele", October 13, 1965; 1 reel-to-reel 5" (Box 17, Reel 200B)
  - Selections from Medieval and Renaissance English - Transcription, August 4, 1993; 1 cassette_tape (Box 17, Cassette 317)
- International Events, 1950-2000; VIII.
  This subseries contains audio recordings of international events which occurred at the University of Pittsburgh from 1950-2000. Highlights of this subseries include a luncheon visit with former Soviet leader Nikita Khrushchev as well as a meeting with business delegates from China, hosted by Chancellor Posvar.
  - Kruschev Luncheon, 1959; 2 reel-to-reel 1 cassette (Box 3, Reel 18)
  - Speech By Polish Secretary, October 24, 1974; 1 reel-to-reel (Box 8, Reel 72)
  - Opening SALT II and 2nd Hour SALT II, Pittsburgh Chamber of Commerce, October 17, 1978; 2 cassette_tapes (Box 11, Cassette 124)
  - Backroom Meeting with Delegation from China, March 7, 1979; 1 cassette_tape (Box 11, Cassette 128)
  - ICA Debriefing - "Iran" - Conducted by Mr. Ivan Alten, February 2, 1959; 1 reel-to-reel (Box 22, Reel 243)
  - ICA Debriefing - "Costa Rica" - Conducted by Eliot Murphy, January 8, 1959; 1 reel-to-reel (Box 22, Reel 244)
  - ICA Debriefing - "Phillipines" - Conducted by Mr. Don McInes, September 13, 1959; 1 reel-to-reel (Box 22, Reel 245)
  - ICA Debriefing - "Brazil" - Conducted by Mr. Bernholz, August 21, 1958; 1 reel-to-reel (Box 22, Reel 246)
  - UN Discussion of "Tibetan Situation" or China's Pressure on the region, 1960; 1 reel-to-reel (Box 24, Reel 263)
  - International Symposium on Global Structure, March 17-19, 1987; 15 cassette_tapes (Box 27, Cassette 280)
  - ACORD Luncheon, May 7, 1987; 2 cassette_tapes (Box 27, Cassette 282)
- Assorted, IX.
  This series contains three miscellaneous audio recordings.
  - Amherst College Commencement - Marina Von Neumann Whitman, 1978; 1 cassette_tape (Box 21, Cassette 224)
    Approximately 2 minutes on side 1 describing Whitman's accomplishments and announcing the conferment of honory Doctor of Laws.
  - Computer Center Slide Show, 1978; 1 reel-to-reel (Box 29, Reel 354)
  - Discussion on Local Recreation - Dub for Students, Professors, and Chancellor Litchfield, undated; 4 reel-to-reel (Box 3, Reel 17)